# Kateryna Butsnieva

### FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

(512) 888-4419



butsnieva@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/butsnieva in



butsnieva.dev



github.com/butsnieva



Austin, TX



# Education and Certifications

The University of Texas

Coding bootcamp Sep 2021

SI Computer School

"QA Professional" course Jul 2019

#### Prydniprovsk State Academy of Civil Architecture and Engineering

Completed coursework towards Bachelor Architecture and Design, 2016

#### Computer Academy "STEP"

Software Development, Software Engineering Dec 2014

## Technical skills

Languages:

HTML, CSS, JavaScript

Database Management:

MySQL, Sequelize, MongoDB, Mongoose

#### Libraries/Frameworks:

jQuery, React.js, Express.js, Bootstrap, UiKit, Tailwind, Selenium, webdriver.io

#### Other Technologies:

Node.js, Socket.io, Handlebars, Git, Bash

## Summary

Ambitious Full Stack Web Developer, effective at using the latest technologies to create efficient and maintainable back-end interfaces and approachable user experiences.

Brings 4+ years of professional experience in QA Testing, ability to design and develop web applications across multiple APIs, third-party integrations and databases.

Self-motivated, able to grasp concepts quickly with minimal supervision, take ownership of problems and follow them through to completion.

## Experience

#### **QA** Engineer

SI Global Solutions | Austin, TX | Mar, 2019 - Current

- Performed Exploratory testing, Functional, Ad-hoc, Usability, Smoke testing, API testing, Regression, and Database validation testing
- Involved in all Agile ceremonies such as planning, stand up, grooming, retrospective.
- Involved in Mobile Web and Native Mobile APP testing on Android, iPad and iPhone, Emulator, Simulator to perform functional, usability, compatibility testing.
- Created and maintained automated regression test scripts using Selenium WebDriver with JavaScript webdriver.io, Chai and Mocha frameworks.
- Coached and assisted new employees with adapting to processes.

#### QA Analyst II

B.WELL | Austin, TX | Oct, 2020 - Mar, 2021

- Performed smoke, functional, integration, compatibility, regression, GUI and release acceptance testing of daily builds on web and mobile devices for Healthcare application.
- Developed test cases for new and existing features.
- Verified FHIR data population and accuracy.
- Validated Mastercard's new identity verification service in user's registration
- Focused on Medical Record Connections and Health Summary experiences.

## Chief Operation Officer (2,5y), <- Sales Manager (9mo)

Global Trans USA | Austin, TX | Jan, 2017 - Jan, 2020

- Mentor and interact with members of staff at all levels.
- Creating, improving, implementing, and enforcing policies and procedures of the organization that will improve operational and financial effectiveness of the company.
- Evaluation of potential mergers, acquisitions, and partnerships.
- Raised profits by 46% within the first 8 months through planning.

#### Manual QA Tester

"CITRUS" Online Gadget Store | Odessa, Ukraine | Feb, 2014 - Mar, 2016

- Responsible for carrying out manual, integration, and compatibility testing for Citrus e-commerce web and mobile web applications.
- Documented test reports and defect reports and presenting conclusions to the
- Participated in the defect review board meetings and weekly team meetings to give and get status updates on the working objectives.